{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Render ",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "lskjkjdsjfjsdfksdhiufgiuguyigigigifguyfufuihigui",
      "description": "koidshigfiugdugfudgufghsdgighiuhiiuiiskjdhfiuhisdiudhigfuigaofodihiuguycgiuaduhwudfu8widjhiuh",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "React eza bo makassss mutu pe esengi pardon  hhgyg333",
      "back": "Not at all, are u sure ?",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "React eza bo makassss mutu pe esengi pardon  hhgyg333",
      "back": "Not at all, are u sure ?",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "React eza bo makassss mutu pe esengi pardon  hhgyg333",
      "back": "Not at all, are u sure ?",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "give me some money ",
      "back": " awwww i dont have any ",
      "id": 9,
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "React eza bo makassss mutu pe esengi pardon  hhgyg333",
      "back": "Not at all, are u sure ?",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "dfgdg",
      "back": "gghff",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "hjfjbjibaj",
      "back": "jhasidhiuhih",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "nbHBHB",
      "back": "GFAYUFUYFY",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "React eza bo makassss mutu pe esengi pardon  hhgyg333",
      "back": "sdfdsfds",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 15
    }
  ]
}